Gerard P. Kuiper papers 1894-1992 (bulk 1949-1973)
University of Arizona Libraries, Special Collections
- Series III: Correspondence, 1923-1974
  - Loyt, Bernard, 1945-1952 (Box 11, Folder 13)
  - Luyten, William J., 1939-1948 (Box 11, Folder 14)
  - Lynds, Beverly, 1957-1971 (Box 11, Folder 15)
  - Mabee to May (Box 11, Folder 16)
  - Mayer to Meszaros (Box 11, Folder 17)
  - Moore to Myers (Box 11, Folder 18)
  - MacMillan Company, 1962-1965 (Box 11, Folder 19)
  - Marcov, A., 1960-1962 (Box 11, Folder 20)
  - Marshall, Thomas Jr., 1949 (Box 11, Folder 21)
  - Martin Company, 1966-1967 (Box 11, Folder 22)
  - Martin Marrietta Aerospace, 1962-1973 (Box 11, Folder 23)
  - Martynov, D. Ja., 1961-1968 (Box 11, Folder 24)
  - Mason, Arnold, 1960-1969 (Box 11, Folder 25)
  - Massachusetts Institute of Technology (MIT), 1961-1968 (Box 11, Folder 26)
  - Mayall, Nicholas, 1961-1973 (Box 11, Folder 27)
  - McDonald, James E., 1961-1970 (Box 11, Folder 28)
  - McDonald Observatory, 1938-1943 (Box 11, Folder 29)
  - McDonald Observatory, 1957-1960 (Box 11, Folder 30)
  - McDonald Observatory, 1961-1970 (Box 11, Folder 31)
  - McDonnell Aircraft Corporation, 1958-1969 (Box 11, Folder 32)
  - McGraw Hill Book Company, 1957-1969 (Box 11, Folder 33)
  - McMillan, Samuel, 1961-1974 (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - McVittie, G.C., 1955-1962 (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Meinel, Aden B., 1950-1969 (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Meinesz, Vening, 1945-1966 (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Melpar Inc., 1962-1963 (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Menzel, Donald H., 1950-1969 (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - Metropolis, Nicholas, 1956-1961 (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - Meteoritical Society, 1953-1974 (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - Michkovitch, A.G., 1956-1961 (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - Middlehurst, Barbara, 1959-1961 (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - Middlehurst, Barbara, 1962-1966 (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - Middlehurst, Barbara, 1967-1973 (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - Mikhailov, A. A., 1959-1965 (Box 12, Folder 13)
  - Millman, Peter, 1952-1973 (Box 12, Folder 14)
  - Minnaert, Marcel Gilles, 1945-1970 (Box 12, Folder 15)
  - Minton, R.B., 1971-1973 (Box 12, Folder 16)
  - Mohler, Orren C., 1952-1968 (Box 12, Folder 17)
  - Moore, Elliott, 1956-1961 (Box 12, Folder 18)
  - Morgan, R. H., 1956 (Box 12, Folder 19)
  - Morgan, W.W., 1943-1973 (Box 12, Folder 20)
  - Mountain Bell - Tumamoc Hill, 1973 (Box 12, Folder 21)
  - Mutual Buying Syndicate Incorporated, 1965; 1970 (Box 12, Folder 22)
  - Naef to Nicalet (Box 12, Folder 23)
  - Nichol to Nya (Box 12, Folder 24)
  - Nacozy, Paul, 1973 (Box 12, Folder 25)
  - Nagy, Bartholomew, 1967-1972 (Box 12, Folder 26)
  - Nassau, Jason J., 1946-1960 (Box 12, Folder 27)
  - National Center for Atmospheric Research, 1967-1970 (Box 12, Folder 28)
  - National Geographic Society, 1957-1972 (Box 12, Folder 29)
  - National Radio Astronomy Observatory, 1956-1959 (Box 12, Folder 30)
  - National Radio Astronomy Observatory, 1960-1969 (Box 12, Folder 31)
  - NATO ASI Planetary Atmospheres, 1972 (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Nature, 1967-1970 (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - Negus de Wys,Jane, 1968 (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - The Netherlands American Foundation, 1933-1966 (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - The Netherlands American University League, 1942-1954 (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Netherlands, 1934-1939 (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - Netherlands, 1940-1966 (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - New York Academy of Sciences, 1951-1970 (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - Newsweek, 1949-1968 (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - Nininger, Harvey H., 1954-1962 (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - Noble, Charles M., 1952-1959 (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - North American Aviation Inc., 1960-1964 (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - Noyes, John C., 1963-1968 (Box 13, Folder 13)
  - Oak Ridge National Laboratory to Oxford University Press (Box 13, Folder 14)
  - Observatory Council, 1947-1951 (Box 13, Folder 15)
  - Office of Aerospace Research Advisory Group, 1963-1964 (Box 13, Folder 16)
  - Ogle, Kenneth N., 1959 (Box 13, Folder 17)
  - Ogorodnikov, K.F., 1959 (Box 13, Folder 18)
  - Olivier, Charles P., 1959 (Box 13, Folder 19)
  - Oort Jan H., 1949-1953 (Box 13, Folder 20)
  - Oort Jan H., 1954-1970 (Box 13, Folder 21)
  - Oosterhoff, Pieter, 1934-1957 (Box 13, Folder 22)
  - Optical Science Center, University of Arizona, 1966-1972 (Box 13, Folder 23)
  - Orway, Frederick L. III, 1961-1965 (Box 13, Folder 24)
  - Owen, Tobias C., 1960-1973 (Box 13, Folder 25)
  - Pace to Perlmutter (Box 13, Folder 26)
  - Perti to Platt (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Podhorsky to Pushkar (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - Page, Thornton, 1947-1959 (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - Page, Thornton, 1960-1973 (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - Palmer, Percy S., 1949-1954 (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - Pannekoek, Antonie, 1934-1968 (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Patrick, David, 1960-1970 (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - Pennsylvania State University, 1958-1959 (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - Percy, Jim, 1966-1973 (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - Pergamon Press, 1952-1970 (Box 14, Folder 10)
  - Perkin Elmer Corporation, 1961-1962 (Box 14, Folder 11)
  - Perkins, Barbara, 1957-1962 (Box 14, Folder 12)
  - Pesek, Luke, 1964-1965 (Box 14, Folder 13)
  - Pfeiffer, John E., 1951-1959 (Box 14, Folder 14)
  - Pikes Peak, 1969-1970 (Box 14, Folder 15)
  - Pliva, Josef, 1955-1968 (Box 14, Folder 16)
  - Pohl, R.W., 1973 (Box 14, Folder 17)
  - Popper, Daniel, 1939-1962 (Box 14, Folder 18)
  - Quibell to Quadrangle Club (Box 14, Folder 19)
  - Radio diffusion Television Belge to Reiffel (Box 14, Folder 20)
  - Reinhold to Roman (Box 14, Folder 21)
  - Roosevelt College to Ryback (Box 14, Folder 22)
  - Rabe, Eugene K., 1952-1958 (Box 14, Folder 23)
  - Raimond, Jean J., 1947-1959 (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Rand McNally, 1954-1972 (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - Ramdic, Leo, 1956-1971 (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - Rao, K. Narahari, 1956; 1964 (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - RCA Victor Company, 1962-1964 (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - Regner, Victor, 1946-1954 (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - Research Corporation of America, 1950-1959 (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - Reuyl, Dirk, 1934-1941 (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - Rhodes, Herbert D., 1960-1972 (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - Rice University, 1966-1967 (Box 15, Folder 10)
  - Richards, W.L., 1961-1965 (Box 15, Folder 11)
  - Richter, Anders, 1960-1964 (Box 15, Folder 12)
  - Richter, Paul H., 1973 (Box 15, Folder 13)
  - Ringwood, Alfred E., 1965-1973 (Box 15, Folder 14)
  - Roach, Frank E., 1950-1954 (Box 15, Folder 15)
  - Rosch, Jean, 1953-1970 (Box 15, Folder 16)
  - Roberts, Walter Orr, 1949-1964 (Box 15, Folder 17)
  - Roemer, Elizabeth, 1965-1974 (Box 15, Folder 18)
  - Rose, Ben, 1957-1958 (Box 15, Folder 19)
  - Ross, Frank E., 1935-1956 (Box 15, Folder 20)
  - Royal Astronomical Society, 1944-1973 (Box 15, Folder 21)
  - Rubingh, Hendrik, 1949-1955 (Box 15, Folder 22)
  - Runcorn, Stanley Keith, 1961-1972 (Box 15, Folder 23)
  - Russell, Henry Norris, 1934-1955 (Box 15, Folder 24)
  - Rutlland, Frederico, 1958-1962 (Box 15, Folder 25)
  - Rybka, Eugeniusz, 1963-1964 (Box 15, Folder 26)
  - Saari, to Schoonmaker Company Inc. (Box 15, Folder 27)
  - Schorr to Sheldon (Box 15, Folder 28)
  - Shell Development to Smith, Bradford A. (Box 15, Folder 29)
  - Smith, Burke to Southwestern Science Exposition (Box 15, Folder 30)
  - Space Science to Steward, Robert (Box 15, Folder 31)
  - Stiger to Szergo (Box 15, Folder 32)
  - Sagan, Carl, 1955-1966 (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - Sagan, Carl, >1967-1973 (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - Sahade, Jorge, 1969-1971 (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - Salisbury, John W., 1959-1972 (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - Sandia Laboratories, 1971-1972 (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - Saturday Review, 1959-1964 (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - Savodoff, Malcolm, 1955-1957 (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - Schaefer, John P., 1971-1973 (Box 16, Folder 8)
  - Schatz, Albert, 1954-1958 (Box 16, Folder 9)
  - Schiemann, Heinrick, 1966-1970 (Box 16, Folder 10)
  - Schlesinger, Frank, 1934-1943 (Box 16, Folder 11)
  - Schorn, Ronald, 1964-1972 (Box 16, Folder 12)
  - Schott, Lucille, 1954-1960 (Box 16, Folder 13)
  - Schwartz, Mortimer, 1963 (Box 16, Folder 14)
  - Schwarzschild, Martin, 1937-1965 (Box 16, Folder 15)
  - Science, 1952-1973 (Box 16, Folder 16)
  - Science Service, 1941-1966 (Box 16, Folder 17)
  - Science America, 1949-1962 (Box 16, Folder 18)
  - Scientia, 1935-1951 (Box 16, Folder 19)
  - Scott, N.W. - Stags Head Studios, 1963 (Box 16, Folder 20)
  - Seyfert, Carl K., 1937-1952 (Box 16, Folder 21)
  - Shaler, Amos, 1938-1940 (Box 16, Folder 22)
  - Shane, Charles Donald, 1946-1962 (Box 16, Folder 23)
  - Shapeley, A.H., 1951-1956 (Box 16, Folder 24)
  - Shapelely, Harold, 1935-1959 (Box 16, Folder 25)
  - Sharonov, V.V., 1961 (Box 16, Folder 26)
  - Sharpless, Stewart, 1966-1970 (Box 16, Folder 27)
  - Shchegolev, D.E., 1960-1961 (Box 16, Folder 28)
  - Shoemaker, Eugene M., 1956-1969 (Box 16, Folder 29)
  - Sigma Xi, 1951-1970 (Box 16, Folder 30)
  - Sill, Godfrey, 1965-1971 (Box 16, Folder 31)
  - Simmons, Melvin J., 1965-1973 (Box 16, Folder 32)
  - Singer, S. Fred, 1952-1972 (Box 16, Folder 33)
  - Sky and Telescope, 1943-1973 (Box 16, Folder 34)
  - Slipher, E.C., 1950-1955 (Box 16, Folder 35)
  - Society of Photo-optical Instrumentation Engineers (SPIE), 1972 (Box 16, Folder 36)
  - Society of the Mayflower Descendants of Arizona, 1964 (Box 16, Folder 37)
  - Sonnet, C.P., 1972-1973 (Box 16, Folder 38)
  - Spitzer, Lyman, 1947-1951 (Box 16, Folder 39)
  - Springer-Verlag, 1963-1965 (Box 16, Folder 40)
  - State of Arizona Atomic Energy Commission, 1966 (Box 16, Folder 41)
  - State of Arizona Atomic Energy Commission, 1967 (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - State of Arizona Atomic Energy Commission, 1968-1969 (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - State of Oregon - Lunar Geological Field Conference, 1965 (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - Stebbins, Joel, 1963-1964 (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - Steiger, Walter, 1950-1951 (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - Stephenson, C. Bruce, 1950 (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - Steward Observatory, 1966-1971 (Box 17, Folder 7)
  - Stickler, W. Hugh, 1950-1951 (Box 17, Folder 8)
  - Stock, Jurgen, 1958-1961 (Box 17, Folder 9)
  - Strand, K. Aa, 1937-1967 (Box 17, Folder 10)
  - Streeter, Jean R., 1958-1967 (Box 17, Folder 11)
  - Streeter, John W., 1951-1955 (Box 17, Folder 12)
  - Strom, Robert G., 1961-1973 (Box 17, Folder 13)
  - Stromgren, Genght, 1937-1959 (Box 17, Folder 14)
  - Struve, Otto, 1933-1939 (Box 17, Folder 15)
  - Struve, Otto, 1940-1947 (Box 17, Folder 16)
  - Struve, Otto, 1948-1965 (Box 17, Folder 17)
  - Suess, Hans, 1950-1969 (Box 17, Folder 18)
  - Sullivan, Walter, 1959-1964 (Box 17, Folder 19)
  - Sweet, Larry, 1972 (Box 17, Folder 20)
  - Swings, Pol, 1940-1953 (Box 17, Folder 21)
  - Swings, Pol, 1954-1973 (Box 17, Folder 22)
  - Tacket to Tokyo (Box 17, Folder 23)
  - Tollin to Tyrrell (Box 17, Folder 24)
  - Tatsch, James, 1959-1970 (Box 17, Folder 25)
  - Texereau, Jean, 1965-1965 (Box 17, Folder 26)
  - Time Incorporated, 1959-1971 (Box 17, Folder 27)
  - Titulaer, Chriet, 1969-1973 (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - Tombaugh, Clyde W., 1946-1961 (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - Trimble, John B., 1966-1972 (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - Trumpler, Robert J., 1935-1957 (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - Turner, Ralph, 1965-1973 (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - Ubell to Urbanowicz (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - Udall, Morris K., 1966-1973 (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - Unitarian Church of Tucson, 1964-1969 (Box 18, Folder 8)
  - United States Central Intelligence Agency (CIA), 1953-1957 (Box 18, Folder 9)
  - United States Civil Service Commission, 1970 (Box 18, Folder 10)
  - United States Department of the Air Force, 1955-1971 (Box 18, Folder 11)
  - United States Department of the Army, 1961-1966 (Box 18, Folder 12)
  - United States Department of the Navy, 1950-1970 (Box 18, Folder 13)
  - United States Federal Communication Commission, 1968 (Box 18, Folder 14)
  - United States Forest Service, 1962-1973 (Box 18, Folder 15)
  - Universidad Nacional de Mexico, Institute de Astronomics, 1973 (Box 18, Folder 16)
  - Universities Space Research Association, 1969-1971 (Box 18, Folder 17)
  - University of Arizona, 1962-1973 (Box 18, Folder 18)
  - University of Chicago, 1948-1959 (Box 18, Folder 19)
  - University of Chicago Alumni Association, 1958-1959 (Box 18, Folder 20)
  - University of Chicago Press, 1939-1973 (Box 18, Folder 21)
  - University of Denver, 1966-1968 (Box 18, Folder 22)
  - University of Pennsylvania Board of Consultants, 1957-1958 (Box 18, Folder 23)
  - University of Texas, 1957-1969 (Box 18, Folder 24)
  - University of Virginia, 1968 (Box 18, Folder 25)
  - Urey, Harold C., 1950-1955 (Box 18, Folder 26)
  - V and V Hackett Studio to Vanderbilt University (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - Varney to Vyssotsky (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - Van Biesbroeck, George, 1932-1973 (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - Van de Hulst, Hendrick, 1945-1950 (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - Van de Kamp, Piet, 1936-1961 (Box 19, Folder 5)
  - Van den Bos, W.H., 1929-1972 (Box 19, Folder 6)
  - Van den Hoek, J., 1934-1953 (Box 19, Folder 7)
  - Van der Bilt, J., 1928-1962 (Box 19, Folder 8)
  - Van Doren, Gerald, 1954-1961 (Box 19, Folder 9)
  - Van Houten, C.J., 1952-1973 (Box 19, Folder 10)
  - Wachendorf to Wertime (Box 19, Folder 11)
  - Wesslink to Williams Bay (Box 19, Folder 12)
  - Williamson, D.H. to Wyse, Art (Box 19, Folder 13)
  - Waland, Robert, 1962-1968 (Box 19, Folder 14)
  - Wallenquist, Ake, 1934-1952 (Box 19, Folder 15)
  - Waller, E.E., 1973-1974 (Box 19, Folder 16)
  - Wamsteker, Willen, 1972-1973 (Box 19, Folder 17)
  - Wanders, A.J.M., 1950-1958 (Box 19, Folder 18)
  - Watkins, Edwin, 1958 (Box 19, Folder 19)
  - Weaver, Albert B., 1963-1973 (Box 19, Folder 20)
  - Weideman, Charles Ray, 1972 (Box 19, Folder 21)
  - Weitbrecht, Robert H., 1933-1951 (Box 19, Folder 22)
  - Weselink, Adriaan, 1933-1951 (Box 19, Folder 23)
  - Westinghouse Electric Company, 1962-1966 (Box 19, Folder 24)
  - Western Gear, 1964-1965 (Box 19, Folder 25)
  - Weyman, Ray J., 1965-1972 (Box 19, Folder 26)
  - Whaley, W. Gordon, 1958-1967 (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - Whipple, Fred L., 1943-1973 (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - Whitaker, Ewen A., 1956-1972 (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - Whitford, Albert F., 1959-1965 (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - White House, Washington, DC., 1961 (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - Wildt, Rubert, 1947-1959 (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - Wilska, Avar P., 1959-1972 (Box 20, Folder 7)
  - Williamson, C.J., 1949-1969 (Box 20, Folder 8)
  - Winzen, Otto C., 1971-1973 (Box 20, Folder 9)
  - Wise, Edward, 1972 (Box 20, Folder 10)
  - Wissell, Charles E. - Not a Meteorite, 1960-1962 (Box 20, Folder 11)
  - Wood, Charles, 1969-1973 (Box 20, Folder 12)
  - Wood, Frank B., 1950-1958 (Box 20, Folder 13)
  - Wood, John, 1961-1971 (Box 20, Folder 14)
  - World Book Encyclopedia, 1956-1964 (Box 20, Folder 15)
  - Wurm, Karl, 1946-1954 (Box 20, Folder 16)
  - Wylie, C.C., 1950-1953 (Box 20, Folder 17)
  - Yamamoto to Young (Box 20, Folder 18)
  - Yale University Press, 1952-1962 (Box 20, Folder 19)
  - Zacharissen to Zissis (Box 20, Folder 20)
  - Zumberge, James H., 1952-1962 (Box 20, Folder 21)
- Series IV: Lunar Planetary Laboratory (LPL): Telescopes and Facilities, 1961-1973.
  This series is arranged alphabetically and contains; photographs, correspondence, documents and blueprints of telescopes, facilities, and observatories which were operated or constructed during the tenure of Gerald Kuiper as the director of LPL
  - History of Catalina Observatory (Mt. Bigelow), 1965 (Box 20, Folder 22)
  - Catalina Site I, 1963-1969 (Box 20, Folder 23)
  - Catalina Site II, 1964-1972 (Box 20, Folder 24)
  - Catalina Site III, 1961-1963 (Box 20, Folder 25)
  - Catalina Observatory 10 inch telescope, 1961-1966 (Box 20, Folder 26)
  - Catalina 21 inch telescope, 1961-1963; 1967 (Box 20, Folder 27)
  - Catalina 27 inch Schmidt telescope, 1967-1973 (Box 20, Folder 28)
  - Catalina 28 inch telescope, 1967-1973 (Box 20, Folder 29)
  - Catalina 28 inch telescope, 1967-1973 (Box 20, Folder 29)
  - Catalina 28 inch telescope, 1967-1973 (Box 20, Folder 29)
  - 60 inch aluminum mirror telescope (Catalina, Mt lemon, Baja.), 1960-1968 (Box 20, Folder 30)
  - Mount Lemon Infrared telescope facilities drawings, undated (Box 20, Folder 31)
  - Mount Lemon Infrared telescope facility, 1967-1973 (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - Mount Lemon Infrared 60 inch telescope removal by Air Force, 1971-1973 (Box 21, Folder 2)
  - Mount Lemon Seeing Tests - George Coyne, 1970-1973 (Box 21, Folder 3)
  - Mount Lemon users group, 1969-1973 (Box 21, Folder 4)
  - Problems with 61 inch telescope, 1973 (Box 21, Folder 5)
  - 61 inch telescope, 1964-1973 (Box 21, Folder 6)
  - 61 inch telescope – Western Gear Contract, 1964-1966 (Box 21, Folder 7)
  - 61 inch telescope dome construction photographs, undated (Box 21, Folder 8)
  - 61 inch telescope observing schedule, undated (Box 21, Folder 9)
  - Photographs taken by the 61” telescope - Mars, Saturn, Jupiter, 1967-1973 (Box 21, Folder 10)
  - Soldier Peak 40 inch telescope, 1968-1973 (Box 21, Folder 11)
  - Spectroscopic Laboratory, 1961 (Box 21, Folder 12)
  - Tumamoc Hill 12½ inch telescope, 1961-1962,1972 (Box 21, Folder 13)
  - Tumamoc Hill 16 inch telescope, 1961-1965 (Box 21, Folder 14)
  - Tumamoc Hill 21 inch telescope, undated (Box 21, Folder 15)
  - [1962], undated (Box 21, Folder 16)
- Series V: International Astronomical Union, 1946-1973.
  This series is arranged chronological and contains meeting minutes from the UAI,
  - Subseries 1: General
    - Correspondence, 1946-1973 (Box 21, Folder 17)
    - Oosterrhoff, P. Th - UAI President, undated (Box 21, Folder 18)
    - Notes, undated (Box 21, Folder 19)
    - Unknown, 1950-1952 (Box 21, Folder 20)
  - Subseries 2: Commission 16 – Study of Planets and Satellites
    - 1947-1952 (Box 21, Folder 21)
    - 1946-1973 (Box 21, Folder 22)
    - 1956-1958 (Box 21, Folder 23)
    - 1956-1958 (Box 21, Folder 24)
    - 1963-1969 (Box 21, Folder 25)
    - 1970-1971 (Box 22, Folder 1)
    - 1972 (Box 22, Folder 2)
    - 1973 (Box 22, Folder 3)
  - Subseries 3: Commission 17 - Lunar Nomenclature
    - 1965-1966 (Box 22, Folder 4)
    - 1967 (Box 22, Folder 5)
    - 1968-1969 (Box 22, Folder 6)
    - 1970-1972 (Box 22, Folder 7)
    - 1972 (Box 22, Folder 8)
    - January 1973-April 1973 (Box 22, Folder 9)
    - May 1973-November 1973 (Box 22, Folder 10)
    - Atlas of the Moon, undated (Box 22, Folder 11)
  - Subseries 4: Commission 20 - Positions and motions of minor planets, comets and satellites
    - 1954-1973 (Box 22, Folder 12)
  - Subseries 5: Commission 26 - High Energy Astrophysics
    - 1950-1961 (Box 22, Folder 13)
  - Subseries 6: Commission 44 - High Energy Astrophysics
    - 1961-1963 (Box 22, Folder 14)
  - Subseries 7: Mars Committee
    - 1953-1955 (Box 22, Folder 15)
  - Subseries 8: United States National Committee
    - 1957-1967 (Box 22, Folder 16)
  - Subseries 9: IAU General Assembly meetings
    - Rome, 1952 (Box 22, Folder 17)
    - Dublin, 1955 (Box 22, Folder 18)
    - Moscow - 1, 1958 (Box 22, Folder 19)
    - Moscow - 2, 1958 (Box 23, Folder 1)
    - Berkley, CA, 1961 (Box 23, Folder 2)
    - Hamburg, Germany, 1964 (Box 23, Folder 3)
    - Prague, Czechoslovakia, 1967 (Box 23, Folder 4)
    - Sydney, Australia, 1972 (Box 23, Folder 5)
  - Subseries 10: IAU Symposiums
    - Symposium on the Moon, Leningrad, 1960 (Box 23, Folder 6)
    - 11th International Astrophysical Symposium Brighton, England, 1962 (Box 23, Folder 7)
    - Symposium no. 23 Astronomical Observations from Space Vehicles, Liege, Belgium, 1964 (Box 23, Folder 8)
    - Symposium no.40 Planetary Atmospheres Marfa, Texas, 1969 (Box 23, Folder 9)
    - Symposium no. 47,The Moon The University of Newcastle upon Tyne, United Kingdom, 1971 (Box 23, Folder 10)
    - Symposium Poland, 1973 (Box 23, Folder 11)
- Series: VI: National Academy of Science, 1942-1973.
  This series is arranged chronologically and contains correspondence, meeting minutes, and reports.
  - General correspondence, 1941-1953 (Box 23, Folder 12)
  - General correspondence, 1954-1959 (Box 23, Folder 13)
  - General correspondence, 1960-1963 (Box 23, Folder 14)
  - General correspondence, 1964-1965 (Box 23, Folder 15)
  - General correspondence, 1966-1968 (Box 23, Folder 16)
  - General correspondence, 1969-1973 (Box 23, Folder 17)
  - NAS Business Section Meeting Minutes, 1956-1965 (Box 23, Folder 18)
  - NAS Business Section Meeting Minutes, 1966-1974 (Box 23, Folder 19)
  - NAS Space Science Board, 1961-1962 (Box 23, Folder 20)
  - NAS Space Science Board, 1963-1966 (Box 24, Folder 1)
  - NAS Space Science Board, 1967 (Box 24, Folder 2)
  - NAS Space Science Board, 1968-1969 (Box 24, Folder 3)
  - Space Science Board Draft Reports for the Summer Session, 1967 (Box 24, Folder 4)
  - Space Station Conference NAS-Ames. Moffett Field, September 9-10,1970 (Box 24, Folder 5)
- Series VII: National Aeronautics and Space Administration, 1954-1974.
  This series is arranged alphabetically by name and then chronologically by date. It contains correspondence, photographs, reports, conference proceedings, and projects.
  - Subseries 1: Ames Research Center
    - Sub-subseries 1:General correspondence
      - 1959 (Box 24, Folder 6)
      - 1963-1967 (Box 24, Folder 7)
      - 1968-1969 (Box 24, Folder 8)
      - 1970-1973 (Box 24, Folder 9)
    - Sub-subseries 2:Convair 990 (CV-990)
      - High Altitude Flight, 1966-1968 (Box 24, Folder 10)
      - High Altitude Sun Flight Data, Summer 1968 (Box 24, Folder 11)
      - High Altitude Venus Flight Data, 1967 (Box 24, Folder 12)
      - High Altitude Mars Flight Data, 1967 (Box 24, Folder 13)
      - Window Transmittance Data and Gratings used for Sun, 1968 (Box 24, Folder 14)
      - Jet Windows, 1963; 1967 (Box 24, Folder 15)
      - Jet Program, undated (Box 24, Folder 16)
      - Airborne Infrared Telescope, [1967] (Box 24, Folder 17)
      - Observatory Flight Maps, [1966-1967] (Box 24, Folder 18)
      - Photographs, [1966-1967] (Box 24, Folder 19)
      - Airborne Lab Handbook, [1966-1967] (Box 24, Folder 20)
      - Lear Jet High Altitude Program, [1968-1969] (Box 24, Folder 21)
      - 36 inch Airborne Telescope, 1967-1969 (Box 24, Folder 22)
  - Subseries 2: Apollo Project
    - Sub-subseries 1: General correspondence
      - 1960-1962 (Box 25, Folder 1)
      - 1963-1965 (Box 25, Folder 2)
      - 1966-1969 (Box 25, Folder 3)
    - Sub-subseries 2: Apollo Program and Lunar Science.
      - 1970-1973 (Box 25, Folder 4)
  - Subseries 3: Comet Conference NASA and LPL, April 8-9,1970
    - Comet Conference Correspondence, 1970-1973 (Box 25, Folder 5)
    - Comet Conference Proceedings, 1970 (Box 25, Folder 6)
  - Subseries 4: Correspondence.
    - A - S (Box 25, Folder 7)
    - Brunk, William, 1965-1967 (Box 25, Folder 8)
    - Brunk, William, 1968-1969 (Box 25, Folder 9)
    - Brunk, William, 1970-1973 (Box 25, Folder 10)
    - Bryson, Robert P., 1965-1973 (Box 25, Folder 11)
    - Cortright, E.M., 1960-1969 (Box 25, Folder 12)
    - Cunningham, N.W., 1960-1965 (Box 25, Folder 13)
    - Dunbin Maurice, 1965; 1970-1973 (Box 25, Folder 14)
    - Dwornik, Stephen, 1966-1973 (Box 25, Folder 15)
    - Holmes, Donald C., 1963-1965 (Box 25, Folder 16)
    - Jastrow, Robert, 1963-1973 (Box 25, Folder 17)
    - Liddel, Urner, 1962-1967 (Box 25, Folder 18)
    - Moore, Roger, 1960-1964 (Box 25, Folder 19)
    - Morgan, Winnie M., 1963-1966 (Box 25, Folder 20)
    - Newell, Homer E., 1961-1964 (Box 25, Folder 21)
    - Newell, Homer E., 1965-1973 (Box 25, Folder 22)
    - Nicks, Cran W., 1962-1972 (Box 26, Folder 1)
    - O’Keefe, John A., 1959-1960 (Box 26, Folder 2)
    - Smull, T.L.K., 1961-1965 (Box 26, Folder 3)
  - Subseries 5: Goddard Space Flight Center.
    - 1960-1967 (Box 26, Folder 4)
    - 1968-1973 (Box 26, Folder 5)
  - Subseries 6: Marshall Space Flight Center.
    - 1962-1973 (Box 26, Folder 6)
  - Subseries 7: Infrared Astronomy Working Group.
    - 1962-1973 (Box 26, Folder 7)
  - Subseries 8: Jet Propulsion Laboratory
    - 1959-1965 (Box 26, Folder 8)
    - 1966-1973 (Box 26, Folder 9)
  - Subseries 9: Lunar Science Institute
    - 1969-1972 (Box 26, Folder 10)